Guide to the Keith Botsford Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- November 1969 Acquisition, 1961-1967; Series VI; 2.09 linear feet (5 boxes)
  - "Youth in Latin America," typescript carbon, 1963 October 29 (Box 111)
- Restricted Fragile Material, 0.21; (1 box)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted fragile material. Reference surrogates have been substituted in the main files. For further information consult the appropriate curator.
  - Box 1, 1 (Box 112)
  - Box 5, 1 (Box 112)
  - Box 6, 1 (Box 112)
  - Box 8, 1 (Box 112)
  - Box 9, 1 (Box 112)
  - Box 10, 1 (Box 112)
  - Box 12, 1 (Box 112)
  - Box 13, 1 (Box 112)
  - Box 14, 1 (Box 112)
  - Box 16, 1 (Box 112)
  - Box 67, 1 (Box 112)
  - Box 69, 1 (Box 112)
  - Box 80, 1 (Box 112)
  - Box 82, 1 (Box 112)
  - Box 83, 1 (Box 112)
  - Box 84, 1 (Box 112)
  - Box 85, 1 (Box 112)
  - Box 107, 1 (Box 112)